https://www.bluewaterropes.com/privacy-terms-and-conditions/

AccountCart
Toggle navigation
ABOUTCommunitySupportContact Search
RecreationalIndustrialABOUTCommunitySupportContactPrivacy, Terms and ConditionsTerms and ConditionsThe following Terms and Conditions apply to the use of this Web site as well as all transactions conducted through the site.Privacy PolicyBlueWater Ropes use of personal information that you may submit to BlueWater Ropes through this Web site is governed by the BlueWater Ropes Privacy Policy which states, “We respect your privacy. Therefore we never share or sell your personal information with any third parties. Any information collected through this site is intended to be used for this transaction only. Your personal information is secured via SSL (Secure Socket Layer) Technology. Information you may provide on the “Contact” page is not encrypted via SSL.” Shipping & DeliveryShipping charges are calculated for lower 48 U.S. destinations only. For shipping to Alaska, Hawaii or outside of the U.S., you will need to contact us for shipping charges. We DO ship to APO and FPO addresses. Shipments to Canada are welcome, but due to freight and tariff calculations, Canadian orders must currently be placed by phone. The risk of loss and title for all merchandise ordered on this Web site pass to you when the merchandise is delivered to the shipping carrier. Sales TaxBlueWater Ropes charges sales tax for merchandise ordered on this Web site based on the applicable state sales tax rate and the location to which the order is being shipped. Return PolicyRock Climbing Gear and other LIFE SUPPORT equipment is only returnable if it is unopened, unused and in the original packaging and is in resellable condition. All return requests must be made within 30 days of delivery of product. Refunds DO not include the freight costs. Please contact BlueWater Ropes for return instructions AND an RA number BEFORE returning merchandise. We’re here to help, so please call.CommunityHear the stories of the men and women who rely on BlueWater Ropes to conquer some of the world's most difficult climbs.
STATSFollow in the footsteps of our athletes to find the next challenge to test your limits.
STORIESDiscover the tales of how ordinary people transformed into extraordinary climbers.
VIDEOSFollow our team members on the adventures that aren't in the guidebook.
INSPIRATIONFeel inspired and motivated by those overcoming incredible odds and adversity.
More about communityThe Confidence To ClimbBlueWater's industry-leading innovations began six generations ago and continue today in their family-owned & operated factory in the USA, where their unwavering commitment to hand-crafted manufacturing processes deliver durable, state-of-the-art products at the fairest prices. Our StoryGeneral InfoAboutRope CareFind RetailersNews / EventsCustomer ServiceFAQContact UsMy AccountPoliciesShippingReturnsPrivacyTerms of UseSpecial Offers
Leave this field empty if you're human: Connect with us Copyright 2019 BlueWater Ropes. Web Design by SHERPA Global.
